<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Twelfth Task</string>
    <string name="image">image</string>
    <string name="dog">Golden Retrievers trace their history back to Scotland.\n
        As sporting dogs, Golden Retrievers need lots of exercise.\n
        They’re a hard-working breed.\n
        Golden Retrievers make top-notch therapy dogs.\n
        Past puppyhood, Golden Retrievers often stay young at heart.\n
        Golden Retrievers love to eat.\n
        Golden Retrievers are naturally mouthy.\n
        When carrying objects, they’re known for their soft mouths.\n
        Goldens shine in event competitions.\n
        Golden Retrievers are perennially popular pets.\n
        Golden Retrievers love to run around and play outside.
        They love water and tend to jump in whenever they get the chance!
        Golden Retrievers also love to tug on things with their mouths, whether sticks or toys.
        In fact, Golden Retrievers can pretty much do it all!\n
        Golden Retrievers are some of the most intelligent dogs we have.
        In fact, they are the 4th smartest dog breed for obedience and working intelligence.
        But what makes the Golden Retriever truly smart is their keen ability to communicate and read human emotions.</string>
    <string name="chameleon">Chameleons have eyes in the backs of their heads\n
        Chameleons come in a lot of different shapes and sizes\n
        Most chameleons eat on things you would not want to find on your dinner plate\n
        Chameleons have good eyesight for a lizard\n
        Chameleons take a while to hatch, and don’t live very long</string>
    <string name="dinosaur">Dinosaurs are a group of reptiles that have lived on Earth for about 245 million years.\n
        In 1842, the English naturalist Sir Richard Owen coined the term Dinosauria, derived from the Greek deinos, meaning fearfully great, and sauros, meaning lizard.\n
        Dinosaur fossils have been found on all seven continents.\n
        All non-avian dinosaurs went extinct about 66 million years ago.\n
        There are roughly 700 known species of extinct dinosaurs.\n
        Modern birds are a kind of dinosaur because they share a common ancestor with non-avian dinosaurs.</string>
    <string name="snake">They have a very big family\n
        They are solar-powered and rely fully on external heat or light sources\n
        Not all snakes lay eggs\n
        Snakes do not have eyelids\n
        They smell with their tongues\n
        Their table manners are different than ours\n
        Snakes have 5 forms of locomotion</string>
    <string name="spider">All spiders produce silk\n
        Karakurt is the most venomous spider in North America. Their venom is about 15 times stronger than rattlesnake venom,
        and uses a chemical called alpha-latrotoxin to overwhelm nerve cells and cause immense pain.
        When the alpha-latrotoxin reaches a person’s nerve cell, the nerve dumps all of its signaling chemicals at once,
        overwhelming its neighbors. In addition to pain, the a bite can cause swelling around the wound, severe cramping, sweating and chills.</string>

</resources>